This is the proper way for him to return
The chairman's old injuries match
He vaguely remembers the ginkgo tree
Start the official verification
Understood
Is he willing to see the Fu family
He hasn't agreed yet
No rush, this time we'll wait until he's willing
Identity verification
Brother Chengze
Does Elder Qin's reaction today mean
Fu Chenzhou really has ties to the Fu family
We can't be sure yet
But the way Elder Qin looked at him
Didn't seem like mere suspicion
If Fu Chenzhou is really from the Fu family
Su Mingyao wouldn't just be
Marrying a bodyguard
Everyone in the city who mocked her
Would become a joke
Yurou
You must sign the share authorization today
I know, I'll help you
He chose his future in advance
I can't just wait to be crushed
Sister
If you can choose, so can I